<!--  Generated on Tue, 21 Sep 2021 12:52:07 +0200  -->
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
<channel>
<atom:link href="https://steamcommunity.com/games/1172620" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<title>Sea of Thieves RSS Feed</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://steamcommunity.com/games/1172620 ]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ Events and Announcements for Sea of Thieves ]]>
</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<generator>Steam Community RSS</generator>
<image>
<url>https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1172620/header.jpg</url>
<title>Sea of Thieves</title>
<link>https://steamcommunity.com/games/1172620</link>
</image>
<item>
<title>Earn the Borderlands Inspired Mayhem Ship Set Now!</title>
<description><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/5feef3157e9759fa1751acf868ff167b7d236ca9.jpg" /><br>Cause mischief on the <i>Sea of Thieves</i> and earn the Mayhem ship set inspired by Gearbox Software<br>During the Xbox Gamescom Stream, <i>Sea of Thieves</i> surprised players with a stunning ship set designed in collaboration with the team over at Gearbox Software. Pirates will be able to earn the full Mayhem ship set by taking part in the Making Mayhem event, live from now until September 7! <br><br><div onclick="javascript:ReplaceWithYouTubeEmbed( this );" data-youtube="YmqDKLTZyjM" class="sharedFilePreviewYouTubeVideo sizeFull"><img class="sharedFilePreviewYouTubeVideo sizeFull" src="https://steamcommunity.com/public/shared/images/responsive/youtube_16x9_placeholder.gif"/><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/YmqDKLTZyjM?fs=1&modestbranding=1&rel=0" allowFullScreen="1" frameBorder="0"></iframe></div><br>Head to the <i>Sea of Thieves</i> <a class="bb_link" href="https://steamcommunity.com/games/1172620/partnerevents/preview/2962792816994204395" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" >website</a> for a full list of chaotic challenges you can tackle to unlock this eye-catching crossover livery. <br></description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://steamcommunity.com/games/1172620/announcements/detail/2962792816994204396 ]]>
</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 17:45:16 +0000</pubDate>
<author>MrJordanAP</author>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://steamcommunity.com/games/1172620/announcements/detail/2962792816994204396</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title> Thank You for Supporting Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</title>
<description><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/e74aaa376183e9cd877b6e4d995d6261fbb284c5.jpg" /><br>It’s been over a month since we released <i><span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</a></i> into the wild blue yonder as part of Season Three, and since that emotional <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">launch day</a> we’ve been bowled over by the response from the <i>Sea of Thieves</i> community. From your reactions on social media to your fan art and stories of exploring the five new Tall Tales, it’s been amazing – and all this excitement resulted in our busiest ever month on the seas, with June seeing 4.8 million active pirates out on the water!<br><br>To all of you who’ve recently cast off for the very first time, jumped back in after a break or simply never stepped away from your regular Voyages, thank you from all of us and we hope that <i>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</i> (and the <a class="bb_link" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u7Z0Pw-95tc" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" >surprise</a> of its unveiling!) was everything you could have wanted from a crossover on this scale.<br><br>Of course, the <i>Sea of Thieves</i> team have also been listening to your feedback and working hard to improve and balance the gameplay throughout the new Tall Tales, with a string of downloadable hotfixes released since Season Three’s launch – and our August update continues to make improvements across the board. Our players’ support has been invaluable in helping us determine what to focus on as we continue to fine-tune the whole <i>Sea of Thieves</i> experience.<br><br>As we wanted to thank all of you face-to-face for spending time with us (and Captain Jack Sparrow, Davy Jones and the rest of our special guests) on the seas this Season, we sat our Creative Director Mike Chapman in front of the camera with a message of thanks to pirates new and returning!<br><br><div onclick="javascript:ReplaceWithYouTubeEmbed( this );" data-youtube="hXZ7WjZ0vOg" class="sharedFilePreviewYouTubeVideo sizeFull"><img class="sharedFilePreviewYouTubeVideo sizeFull" src="https://steamcommunity.com/public/shared/images/responsive/youtube_16x9_placeholder.gif"/><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/hXZ7WjZ0vOg?fs=1&modestbranding=1&rel=0" allowFullScreen="1" frameBorder="0"></iframe></div><br>If you’re fully invested in living the pirate life after journeying with Jack Sparrow, a whole world of adventure awaits – and there are so many places to go. Here are just a few of the exciting things that you can keep in mind for your next sail: <br><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 11 previously established Tall Tales that see you exploring not only the islands within the Devil’s Shroud but beyond, journeying through history and legend to find out more about the colourful characters that call the Sea of Thieves their home.<br></li><li> New Seasonal Trials introduced in each Season, with Season Three’s selection encouraging exploration of those earlier Tall Tales – check them out to boost your Seasonal progression and unlock rewards on the way to level 100!<br></li><li> Engaging world events that affect <i>Sea of Thieves’</i> shared world, like battles with the spectral armada of Captain Flameheart or the appearances of challenging Ashen Lords.<br></li><li> Skeleton Forts filled with skeletons to conquer and treasure to plunder – from the haunted Fort of the Damned to the loot-laden Forts of Fortune.<br></li><li> Trading Company Voyages including all the new additions from the last year of free content updates, from sunken plunder waiting to be recovered from the Merchant Alliance’s Lost Shipments to the Gold Hoarders’ Treasure Vault Voyages that give you a Golden Wayfinder compass and send you off in search of a big score.<br></li><li> Tales of legendary pirates and achievements inspired by real players, all of which can be uncovered by tracking down Umbra’s Legends of the Sea.</li></ul>Ready to raise anchor? As an extra bonus, the weekend of August 20th-23rd plays host to our latest Gold &amp; Glory Weekend, offering double gold and reputation gains along with Seasonal Renown boosts for all treasure handed in to the Trading Companies!<br><br><div onclick="javascript:ReplaceWithYouTubeEmbed( this );" data-youtube="LkOIumXHKP8" class="sharedFilePreviewYouTubeVideo sizeFull"><img class="sharedFilePreviewYouTubeVideo sizeFull" src="https://steamcommunity.com/public/shared/images/responsive/youtube_16x9_placeholder.gif"/><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LkOIumXHKP8?fs=1&modestbranding=1&rel=0" allowFullScreen="1" frameBorder="0"></iframe></div><br>You'll also find a brand new crop of Disney’s <i>Pirates of the Caribbean</i> cosmetics in the Pirate Emporium as part of August’s <i>Sea of Thieves</i> update: transform your ship into a vessel of purgatory with the Cursed Ferryman Ship Collection, make pirates think they’re facing a harbinger of the abyss with the Davy Jones Cursed Costume Set, or adopt a simian sidekick dressed like that dread figure himself in the form of the Condemned Captain Monkey pet. For more on these and all the quality of life improvements made in August’s update, check out the full <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">release notes.</a><br><br>Whatever heading you take and whatever favourites you find, this year promises even more fun coming to <i>Sea of Thieves</i>, so follow our social channels and be among the first to know what’s on the horizon: <a class="bb_link" href="https://twitter.com/SeaOfThieves" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" >Twitter</a>, <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">Facebook</a>, <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">Instagram</a>, <a class="bb_link" href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCtt2JqBTG-KoBae4F0Ay2tg" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" >YouTube</a>, <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">Twitch</a>, <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">TikTok</a> and the official <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">Forums</a> and <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">Discord</a> server. If you still have burning questions about our epic collaboration with Disney to bring their <i>Pirates of the Caribbean</i> franchise into <i>Sea of Thieves</i>, or you’re still considering a foray into our shared pirate world, check out our dedicated <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;"><i>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</i> FAQ</a>! It covers everything from embarking on the five new Tall Tales to finding resources on becoming a better pirate.<br><br><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/5fb4c5709529604bac6465d7248bc999c5cf68a4.jpg" /><br><br>That’s it from us for now – thanks again from everyone on the <i>Sea of Thieves</i> team, and we'll see you on the seas!<br></description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://steamcommunity.com/games/1172620/announcements/detail/5148163999418338929 ]]>
</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 20:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
<author>MrJordanAP</author>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://steamcommunity.com/games/1172620/announcements/detail/5148163999418338929</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sea of Thieves Sale June 22nd-July 8th</title>
<description><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/96f416acdbc8b352d26caebcfe53807d4475eff0.png" /><br>For those of you yet to venture out onto the Sea of Thieves, the game will be on sale from 22nd June (6:00pm BST) – 8th July to commemorate the launch of <i>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</i>. There has never been a better time to jump into <i>Sea of Thieves</i>, so what are you waiting for? We’ll see you on the seas!<br><br>The Season Three update including <i>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</i> will be available for free to all <i>Sea of Thieves</i> players who have bought the game on Steam. For more information on Season Three when it arrives on June 22, visit the <i>Sea of Thieves</i> <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">website</a>. <br><br>New to <i>Sea of Thieves</i>? Join the fun with our Maiden Voyage, a narrative-driven tutorial experience. New players will begin their travels within this scenario – and more tips can be picked up from our online <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">Pirate Academy</a>, which provides invaluable information on topics ranging from sailing to swordplay. Learn more about <i>Sea of Thieves</i> at <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">http://www.xbox.com/seaofthieves</a>, or join the ongoing adventure at <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">http://www.seaofthieves.com</a> where you can embark on an epic journey with one of gaming’s most welcoming communities!<br></description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://steamcommunity.com/games/1172620/announcements/detail/3001067707362920878 ]]>
</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 10:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
<author>MrJordanAP</author>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://steamcommunity.com/games/1172620/announcements/detail/3001067707362920878</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Join Captain Jack Sparrow in Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</title>
<description><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/a8d96206b8c1f94b73509105403432c9825bb098.png" /><br>Today is a monumental day for <i>Sea of Thieves</i>. We’re not only celebrating the arrival of Season Three with its raft of new Events, improvements and rewards, but also the epic collaboration that is <i>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</i> – an incredible new story campaign that brings <i>Pirates of the Caribbean</i> sailing into the Sea of Thieves. <br><br>Like previous Seasons in <i>Sea of Thieves</i>, Season Three comes free of charge to all players and includes 100 levels of rewards to be earned by sailing the seas and steadily increasing your Renown. Time-limited Events can boost your Renown, as can Trials: wide-ranging sets of Deeds refreshed for Season Three as you take on incoming adversaries and Tall Tales. Season Three’s Plunder Pass is available to buy separately, adding all-new premium treasures to the Seasonal reward pool! Learn more in our <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">Seasons Explained</a> and <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">Plunder Pass Explained</a> articles.<br><br><div class="bb_h3">Adventure with Jack Sparrow</div><br>At the heart of Season Three is <i>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</i> – a collection of five carefully crafted Tall Tales forming an original story where Jack Sparrow stars alongside our pirate crews. Players will journey to strange, ethereal realms and dive deep below the waves on their quest to defeat the nefarious Davy Jones, who has pursued Jack to the Sea of Thieves and threatens to destroy the pirate life unless his schemes can be stopped.<br> <br><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/e541ee92038a3e815d1ea7e29b85f1cd4b49f0f1.jpg" /><br><br>Packed with vast new locations, an assortment of dangerous new enemies, secrets to uncover and cosmetic rewards to earn, <i>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</i> is an exhilarating experience that we hope players will enjoy diving into alongside the legendary Captain Jack Sparrow. <br><br><div class="bb_h3">New Dangers Await</div><br>The seas are always changing, and the new enemies you’ll encounter during Season Three aren’t just confined to the latest Tall Tales. Trident-wielding Sirens from the deep, nimble pirate Phantoms and lumbering Ocean Crawlers have awoken throughout the world, meaning that new threats are liable to arise during any journey across the seas. Be ready to think on your feet and learn new strategies to safeguard your life, your ship and your treasure! Cunning pirates can even snare a Trident of Dark Tides from a fallen Siren and wield it themselves, an addition to the usual arsenal which is sure to prove useful when facing these new foes.<br><br><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/ceb38d7eb377704028bf6c9bc19d23b0d323d017.jpg" /><br> <br><div class="bb_h3">Find Eternal Freedom</div><br>To celebrate the arrival of Jack Sparrow and his devoted crew, Season Three sees the Pirate Emporium hosting special items themed around <i>Pirates of the Caribbean</i>. The Captain Jack Sparrow Crew Set contains costumes inspired by Jack’s own iconic look along with outfits representing his loyal shipmates, while the Eternal Freedom Ship Collection lets you pay homage to Jack’s seafaring pride and joy. An assortment of new Jack Sparrow Emotes give some classic <i>Sea of Thieves</i> gestures a new lease of life, and last but not least, the faithful Prison Dog finds a well-deserved home within our collection of canine pets.<br><br>Elsewhere, players who pick up the Season Three Plunder Pass will unlock extra rewards as they earn Renown, all of which – from the Shining Pegasus Costume and weapons to premium picks from the electrifying Thunderous Fury ship set – are so new that not even the Emporium has them in stock yet!<br> <br><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/4c4f6a1d499843b7cfcee4c6fad3018adc216b42.jpg" /><br><br><div class="bb_h3">Find Out More</div><br>Unveiled last week, the gameplay trailer for <i>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</i> provides a tantalising look at this crossover adventure to whet the appetites of players preparing to download the update, as does the special behind-the-scenes Xbox broadcast that offers sightings from two of the brand new Tall Tales.<br><br>The Season Three update including <i>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</i> will be available for free to all <i>Sea of Thieves</i> players who have bought the game on Steam. For more information on Season Three at launch on June 22, visit the <i>Sea of Thieves</i> <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">website</a>.<br><br><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/b9a4509cd955b892d3833a079927f361aa306d87.png" /><br> <br>New to <i>Sea of Thieves</i>? Join the fun with our Maiden Voyage, a narrative-driven tutorial experience. New players will begin their travels within this scenario – and more tips can be picked up from our online <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">Pirate Academy</a>, which provides invaluable information on topics ranging from sailing to swordplay. Learn more about <i>Sea of Thieves</i> at <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">http://www.xbox.com/seaofthieves</a>, or join the ongoing adventure at <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">http://www.seaofthieves.com</a> where you can embark on an epic journey with one of gaming’s most welcoming communities!<br><br>© 2021 Microsoft Corporation.<br>© Disney.<br></description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://steamcommunity.com/games/1172620/announcements/detail/3001067707363353730 ]]>
</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 13:08:21 +0000</pubDate>
<author>MrJordanAP</author>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://steamcommunity.com/games/1172620/announcements/detail/3001067707363353730</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Join the Rare Crew for an Exclusive Look at Sea of Thieves: A Pirates Life</title>
<description><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/0f94789a42f23cff477221616b87b878801174cb.jpg" /><br><i>Sea of Thieves</i> Season Three launches later this month, and with it comes <i>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</i> – an epic original story that brings Captain Jack Sparrow and his crew sailing in from beyond the horizon to spark new adventures spanning five narrative-driven Tall Tales. <br><br>Following its announcement at E3 with a stunning cinematic trailer, we’ve already hinted at what’s in store for those brave buccaneers ready to stand alongside Jack Sparrow in one of the Sea of Thieves’ greatest battles yet. Today’s special Xbox broadcast catches up with the teams behind this magical collaboration to offer some rousing insights into its creation. Team members from both Rare and Walt Disney Games talk freely about the vision, the ambition, the care and attention poured into every aspect of this dream crossover – and just some of the features they’re most excited for fans of both franchises to experience. <br><br><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/e74aaa376183e9cd877b6e4d995d6261fbb284c5.jpg" /><br><br>The special broadcast also dives deep into the gameplay of the first two Tall Tales where players will brave the Sea of the Damned, amongst many other challenges, and teases more about what’s to come when <i>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</i> headlines Season Three at launch on June 22. <br><br>Join the team on this journey behind the scenes by watching the video here: <br><br><div onclick="javascript:ReplaceWithYouTubeEmbed( this );" data-youtube="iK6R8709BzE" class="sharedFilePreviewYouTubeVideo sizeFull"><img class="sharedFilePreviewYouTubeVideo sizeFull" src="https://steamcommunity.com/public/shared/images/responsive/youtube_16x9_placeholder.gif"/><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/iK6R8709BzE?fs=1&modestbranding=1&rel=0" allowFullScreen="1" frameBorder="0"></iframe></div><br><div class="bb_h3">Find Out More </div><br>The Season Three update including <i>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</i> will be available for free to all <i>Sea of Thieves</i> players who have bought the game on Steam. For more information on Season Three when it arrives on June 22, visit the <i>Sea of Thieves</i> <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">website</a>. <br><br>New to <i>Sea of Thieves</i>? Join the fun with our Maiden Voyage, a narrative-driven tutorial experience. New players will begin their travels within this scenario – and more tips can be picked up from our online <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">Pirate Academy</a>, which provides invaluable information on topics ranging from sailing to swordplay. Learn more about <i>Sea of Thieves</i> at <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">http://www.xbox.com/seaofthieves</a>, or join the ongoing adventure at <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">http://www.seaofthieves.com</a> where you can embark on an epic journey with one of gaming’s most welcoming communities!</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://steamcommunity.com/games/1172620/announcements/detail/3001067707357120730 ]]>
</link>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 22:33:26 +0000</pubDate>
<author>MrJordanAP</author>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://steamcommunity.com/games/1172620/announcements/detail/3001067707357120730</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>See the Ultimate Pirate Crossover in Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life Gameplay</title>
<description><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/60b16a7185b62af50f3045ff81275e27e2231fd2.jpg" /><br><br>Today we’re excited to take the next step on our journey to delivering <i>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</i> as the headline feature of the upcoming Season Three, premiering footage of the gameplay that fans can expect to enjoy as they dive into five all-new Tall Tales, facing excitement and peril in equal measure. <br><br>This unforgettable adventure alongside Captain Jack Sparrow will take players across, below and beyond the Sea of Thieves to battle new kinds of enemies, many of which are here to stay and will spread out beyond these Tall Tales to menace pirates all across the seas. Players will also travel to vast new realms, pick their way through crumbling ruins and forsaken pirate towns, and experience twists and encounters yet to be revealed. Watch our new gameplay trailer for a taste of the action:<br><br><div onclick="javascript:ReplaceWithYouTubeEmbed( this );" data-youtube="s8dT1VnuliM" class="sharedFilePreviewYouTubeVideo sizeFull"><img class="sharedFilePreviewYouTubeVideo sizeFull" src="https://steamcommunity.com/public/shared/images/responsive/youtube_16x9_placeholder.gif"/><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/s8dT1VnuliM?fs=1&modestbranding=1&rel=0" allowFullScreen="1" frameBorder="0"></iframe></div><br>We can’t wait for players to experience <i>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</i> for themselves, setting sail with Jack Sparrow, battling Sirens and Ocean Crawlers and racing to stop the schemes of the nefarious Davy Jones when Season Three arrives on June 22.<br><br><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/1a5c8b6a88c9a49a2fcd6e23aa7fe05a5550fa2a.jpg" /><br><br>Fans and gamers keen to see more of <i>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</i> are encouraged to join us for a special Xbox broadcast on June 20, venturing behind the scenes of this momentous collaboration and offering a world-exclusive look at the first two Tall Tales!<br><br><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/56396b6254248f878385973ed8658baaec09431a.jpg" /><br><br><div class="bb_h3">Find Out More</div><br>The Season Three update including <i>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</i> will be available for free to all <i>Sea of Thieves</i> players who have bought the game on Steam. For more information on Season Three when it arrives on June 22, visit the <i>Sea of Thieves</i> <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">website</a>. <br><br>New to <i>Sea of Thieves</i>? Join the fun with our Maiden Voyage, a narrative-driven tutorial experience. New players will begin their travels within this scenario – and more tips can be picked up from our online <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">Pirate Academy</a>, which provides invaluable information on topics ranging from sailing to swordplay. Learn more about <i>Sea of Thieves</i> at <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">http://www.xbox.com/seaofthieves</a>, or join the ongoing adventure at <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">http://www.seaofthieves.com</a> where you can embark on an epic journey with one of gaming’s most welcoming communities!<br><br>© 2021 Microsoft Corporation.<br><br>© Disney.<br><br></description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://steamcommunity.com/games/1172620/announcements/detail/3001067707345940069 ]]>
</link>
<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 17:59:10 +0000</pubDate>
<author>MrJordanAP</author>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://steamcommunity.com/games/1172620/announcements/detail/3001067707345940069</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life Images Unleashed As Two Pirate Worlds Collide</title>
<description><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/22032d2d297484969700c441e50b4eb29251af8b.jpg" /><br>As part of a momentous collaboration between Xbox, Rare and Disney, we recently announced that <i>Sea of Thieves</i>’ upcoming Season Three update will be headlined by <i>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</i> – an all-new set of narrative-driven Tall Tales that bring Captain Jack Sparrow and his infamous crew from beyond the horizon to spark an incredible new adventure.<br><br>We’ve already debuted a cinematic trailer to give players a taste of what to expect from the story, but we know that fans are eager to see more of the exciting gameplay, enthralling new enemies and unforgettable locations they’ll encounter and explore as they work to foil the schemes of the notorious Davy Jones.<br><br><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/e541ee92038a3e815d1ea7e29b85f1cd4b49f0f1.jpg" /><br><br>So today, we’re thrilled to premiere a fresh selection of images from <i>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</i>. They offer a closer look at Jack Sparrow, some of the memorable places that players will travel to in his company and just a few of the traps and threats that lie in wait.<br><br><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/5fb4c5709529604bac6465d7248bc999c5cf68a4.jpg" /><br><br>We’re also delighted to announce that we will premiere the <i>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</i> Gameplay Trailer during the Xbox Games Showcase: Extended broadcast on Thursday, June 17. Learn more about <i>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</i> by tuning in at 10am PT on the day – and stay tuned for more details ahead of the update’s launch!<br><br><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/e01467a60562bf71c6d9c9561f5987b7e1dfc665.jpg" /><br><br><div class="bb_h3">Find Out More</div><br>The Season Three update including <i>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</i> will be available for free to all <i>Sea of Thieves</i> players who have bought the game on Steam. For more information on Season Three when it arrives on June 22, visit the <i>Sea of Thieves</i> <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">website</a>.<br><br><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/70049257261dc0e14e84cc050e4448cf04fe1baf.jpg" /><br><br>New to <i>Sea of Thieves</i>? Join the fun with our Maiden Voyage, a narrative-driven tutorial experience. New players will begin their travels within this scenario – and more tips can be picked up from our online <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">Pirate Academy</a>, which provides invaluable information on topics ranging from sailing to swordplay. Learn more about <i>Sea of Thieves</i> at <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">http://www.xbox.com/seaofthieves</a>, or join the ongoing adventure at <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">http://www.seaofthieves.com</a> where you can embark on an epic journey with one of gaming’s most welcoming communities!<br><br>© 2021 Microsoft Corporation.<br><br>© Disney.</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://steamcommunity.com/games/1172620/announcements/detail/3001067707342205117 ]]>
</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 16:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
<author>MrJordanAP</author>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://steamcommunity.com/games/1172620/announcements/detail/3001067707342205117</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate's Life</title>
<description><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/a79a567a4b4911dd677d8ae1016affc352d82093.png" /><br><br>Today, Rare and Xbox are thrilled to announce an exciting collaboration with Disney, as the award-winning <i>Sea of Thieves</i> and <i>Pirates of the Caribbean</i> join forces at last. This monumental crossover will see Captain Jack Sparrow and his infamous crew arrive from beyond the horizon to spark an epic new adventure on the Sea of Thieves. Watch the announcement trailer for <i>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</i> right here:<br><br><div onclick="javascript:ReplaceWithYouTubeEmbed( this );" data-youtube="kIcg4VQJXB8" class="sharedFilePreviewYouTubeVideo sizeFull"><img class="sharedFilePreviewYouTubeVideo sizeFull" src="https://steamcommunity.com/public/shared/images/responsive/youtube_16x9_placeholder.gif"/><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/kIcg4VQJXB8?fs=1&modestbranding=1&rel=0" allowFullScreen="1" frameBorder="0"></iframe></div><br><br>Unfolding across five incredible tales packed with secrets and side-quests, this new campaign gives players a lovingly crafted story to play solo or with their crew. <i>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</i> will be free for all players and will launch as the cornerstone of <i>Sea of Thieves Season</i> Three on June 22. <br><br><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/f3565565b88789ed0603853cc763fa2ffe2197be.jpg" /><br> <br><div class="bb_h3">Two Legends Collide</div><br><i>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</i> is the game’s most ambitious story-driven campaign to date. Players will go on a quest to free Jack Sparrow from his prison and witness the power of the world’s greatest Pirate Treasure, which Jack just so happens to have stolen. Jack is being pursued by his old enemy, the notorious Davy Jones, and their arrival on the Sea of Thieves will ultimately spell disaster if Jones and his forces aren’t stopped.<br><br>These iconic characters are here for much more than cameo appearances, and we’ve worked alongside Walt Disney Games to craft a compelling original narrative that doesn’t just bring two worlds together, but explores what makes each of them special. <br><br><i>Sea of Thieves’</i> Executive Producer Joe Neate explains: “<i>Sea of Thieves</i> aims to immerse players in a fantastical depiction of the pirate life, filled with colourful characters and vibrant locations to explore. The sense of fun, wonder and the imaginative spirit that we hold real affection for in the world of <i>Pirates of the Caribbean</i> always felt like it could be complementary to the world of <i>Sea of Thieves</i>, and we’ve striven alongside the teams at Disney to celebrate this.” <br> <br><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/8958432eec74bd7b35b95de403cdf1f91f07b3a2.jpg" /><br><br>Mike Chapman, <i>Sea of Thieves’</i> Creative Director, was keen to ensure the narrative remained true to the spirit of both universes. “The heart of our story explores what it truly means to be a pirate on the Sea of Thieves, and this has allowed us not only to tap into the deeper meaning of the <i>Pirates of the Caribbean</i> movies and the original attraction, but also allow players to go on adventures with Jack Sparrow, learning more about how he sees the pirate life and his place on the Sea of Thieves. This story moves the <i>Sea of Thieves</i> world forwards in unexpected ways, and it’s been a joy to bring these two worlds together, treating both in a way that feels authentic and delightful to experience.”<br><br><div class="bb_h3">New Dangers Arise</div>Of course, new adventures bring new environments and challenges. As the story progresses, players will battle Davy Jones alongside Captain Jack Sparrow and have the chance to explore memorable locations from both universes – not only extending to <i>Sea of Thieves</i> and Disney’s <i>Pirates of the Caribbea</i>n film franchise but the famous park attractions that have been thrilling people for decades. <br> <br><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/987e12ccc5b3cf1baa423fd22431250d16e4cb09.jpg" /><br><br>Players will also be facing grave danger from deadly new enemies wherever they sail. Terrifying Phantoms will require swift reflexes to deal with, while Sirens swarm beneath the waves and wield devastating new weapons of their own. Even the decks of ships might not be safe if there are lumbering Ocean Crawlers around, and these new threats will be appearing all around the Sea of Thieves in future updates, not just during players’ adventures with Jack Sparrow! <br> <br><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/a8d9e309c2172ba71e64c256524a8545f573330e.jpg" /><br><br><div class="bb_h3">Find Out More</div><br>The Season Three update including <i>Sea of Thieves: A Pirate’s Life</i> will be available for free to all <i>Sea of Thieves</i> players who have bought the game on Steam. For more information on Season Three when it arrives on June 22, visit the <i>Sea of Thieves</i> <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">website</a>. <br> <br><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/04e7ddb7b991b8ad0797624e177730869cb6eece.jpg" /><br><br>New to <i>Sea of Thieves</i>? Join the fun with our Maiden Voyage, a narrative-driven tutorial experience. New players will begin their travels within this scenario – and more tips can be picked up from our online <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">Pirate Academy</a>, which provides invaluable information on topics ranging from sailing to swordplay. Learn more about Sea of Thieves at <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">https://www.xbox.com/seaofthieves</a>, or join the ongoing adventure at <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">https://www.seaofthieves.com/</a> where you can embark on an epic journey with one of gaming’s most welcoming communities!<br><br>© 2021 Microsoft Corporation.<br>© Disney.<br></description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://steamcommunity.com/games/1172620/announcements/detail/5392478663047401128 ]]>
</link>
<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 17:23:55 +0000</pubDate>
<author>MrJordanAP</author>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://steamcommunity.com/games/1172620/announcements/detail/5392478663047401128</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Reapers vs. the World</title>
<description><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/e393c7ba37f4968c8b98bc6a1a3bd58eb4f32080.jpg" /><br><br>The Reapers have shifted their focus away from the Gold Hoarders, and now the Order of Souls have issued a rallying call! For the next fortnight, sail as an Emissary on behalf of the Order of Souls and tackle Event-specific goals to earn Season Two Renown along with a range of rewards. Following that, the Merchant Alliance will be under the spotlight, before all three Companies unite against their common foe. <br><br>For the blackhearted Reapers among you, the Event-wide goal is still active! The Reaper’s Bones are keeping note of all Emissary Flags captured and returned to The Reaper’s Hideout and will provide qualifying players (who’ve returned 10 or more Flags as Reaper Emissaries themselves) with a cosmetic reward depending on which Trading Company suffers the greatest losses. Keep an eye on the <i>Sea of Thieves</i> social channel updates to see which reward players are on track to receive when the Event ends.<br><br><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/4ae140bd2bfa837b3f3052ea07a9887725ad9027.png" /><br><br>As we have now entered the first full Emissary Ledger period of Season Two, players who’ve earned the previous Ledger rewards for any given Company will now be able to play for their newly introduced Ledger rewards. Log in and track your progress at the dedicated <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">Emissary Ledgers</a> page!<br></description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://steamcommunity.com/games/1172620/announcements/detail/3075373295039247594 ]]>
</link>
<pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 16:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
<author>MrJordanAP</author>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://steamcommunity.com/games/1172620/announcements/detail/3075373295039247594</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sea of Thieves Season Two</title>
<description><div onclick="javascript:ReplaceWithYouTubeEmbed( this );" data-youtube="vFKacfeTMwc" class="sharedFilePreviewYouTubeVideo sizeFull"><img class="sharedFilePreviewYouTubeVideo sizeFull" src="https://steamcommunity.com/public/shared/images/responsive/youtube_16x9_placeholder.gif"/><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/vFKacfeTMwc?fs=1&modestbranding=1&rel=0" allowFullScreen="1" frameBorder="0"></iframe></div><br>With the seasons changing outside, <i>Sea of Thieves</i> is changing too as we enter a new Season of our own! New Events, ways to play and rewards are all coming with the release of Season Two, available now as a free update for all players on Steam.<br><br>Season Two comes free of charge to all players including 100 levels of rewards to be earned, with a purchasable Plunder Pass also available to boost the pool with additional premium rewards. As in the previous Season, you work your way up through the levels by living the pirate life, achieving things in your own way and steadily increasing your Renown. You can gain extra Renown by completing Trials: themed sets of Deeds that cover almost every imaginable action in <i>Sea of Thieves</i>, refreshed for Season Two!<br><br><div class="bb_h3">Season Two Showcase</div><br>The Forts of Fortune have arrived, marked by an ominous new form of Skull Cloud looming in the skies over the Sea of Thieves. These encounters provide an even more rigorous challenge than other Skeleton Forts, with extra explosive potential and ever fiercer foes as the waves of resistance keep coming. Guaranteed Athena’s Treasures and other high-level loot await any crews who can conquer this gauntlet. If you fancy your chances against the undead hordes, keep an eye (and ear) out for the tell-tale signs of this rare encounter emerging as you sail!<br><br>Should you prefer trade to battle, Season Two also brings in new Merchant Alliance Trade Routes. Emissaries can earn their fortune by buying Commodity Crates as cheaply as possible at Outposts, then selling them at another Outpost where those Commodities are highly sought-after. The Merchant Alliance now sell Resource Crates too, so stocking up on bananas, wooden planks and cannonballs has never been easier!<br><br><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/e393c7ba37f4968c8b98bc6a1a3bd58eb4f32080.jpg" /><br><br>To attract more pirates to their cause, the Trading Companies are rolling out brand new rewards for those Emissaries who place highly in their Emissary Ledgers. Not an Emissary yet? They’ll send out a Mysterious Note when you’re eligible to purchase their Emissary Licence and set sail under their Flag.<br>All this along with Season Two’s dramatic time-limited Event, Reapers vs. the World – pitting The Reaper’s Bones against the other Trading Companies in an epic game of Emissary cat and mouse – and more Twitch Drops on the horizon from our <i>Sea of Thieves</i> Partnered streamers!<br><br><div class="bb_h3">Pirate Emporium Plunder</div><br>With a new Season comes a new Plunder Pass, packed with Pirate Emporium items to boost the pool of rewards available via Seasonal progression. Picking up the Plunder Pass adds these premium items to the obtainable rewards for Season Two, including unreleased items like the Black Phoenix Figurehead, Sails and Flag, along with the Popcorn and Backflip emotes. For those looking to hit level 100 this Season, the Plunder Pass is an enticing accoutrement to your adventures!<br><br><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/6d0e68ce5d46fff09b546654c59f2586ac7556fb.jpg" /><br><br>Also new to the Pirate Emporium this month: the opportunity to strike fear into all who sail the Sea of Thieves with the Dark Warsmith collection, comprising a full ship set, a terrifying all-in-one pirate costume and a bundle of red-hot weaponry. Players who want to show off their skills with a blade can do so with the new Dagger Tricks Emote Bundle, but remember – our pirates are trained professionals, don’t try this at home! <br><br><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/37295600/6943e75d632db645294b01d1400da1193f09277d.jpg" /><br><br><div class="bb_h3">Find Out More </div><br>For more information on the <i>Sea of Thieves Season</i> Two update, including full <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">release notes</a>, visit the <i>Sea of Thieves</i> <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">website</a>. The update is available for free to all <i>Sea of Thieves</i> players who have bought the game on Steam, simply download and install the latest <i>Sea of Thieves</i> update to get access.<br><br>New to <i>Sea of Thieves</i>? Find out about the latest free content updates on our <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">What’s New</a> page and pick up some tips from our <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">Pirate Academy</a>, which provides invaluable information on topics ranging from sailing to swordplay as you prepare for your maiden voyage. Learn more about at <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">https://www.xbox.com/seaofthieves</a>, or join the ongoing adventure at <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="L'URL qui collegato è stato rimosso dai nostri filtri, per evitare possibili attacchi tramite phishing e malware.">{COLLEGAMENTO RIMOSSO}</span><a href="#" class="collapsed_link" style="display: none;">https://www.seaofthieves.com/</a> where you can embark on an epic journey with one of gaming’s most welcoming communities!<br></description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://steamcommunity.com/games/1172620/announcements/detail/4710178153975420744 ]]>
</link>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 17:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
<author>MrJordanAP</author>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://steamcommunity.com/games/1172620/announcements/detail/4710178153975420744</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
